// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: "601m4p71a",
    question: "What work should be done before project initiation?",
    answer: "business case for the project",
    options: [
      "PMI doesn't outline work before project initation.",
      "business case for the project",
      "determine project budget",
      "assign a project team"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 4 slide 71."
  },
    {
    numb: "601m4p71b",
    question: "What should be included in a business case?",
    answer: "All of the above.",
    options: [
      "expected benefit",
      "written or verbal value proposition",
      "document that includes problem statement, recommended solution, analysis, feasibility, and alternatives",
      "All of the above."
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 4 slide 71."
  },
    {
    numb: "601m5p78",
    question: "What is the main purpose of the Initiation process group?",
    answer: "define a new project or phase",
    options: [
      "determine a suitable timeline",
      "determine the budget",
      "define a new project or phase",
      "complete the work"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 78."
  },
    {
    numb: "601m5p2a",
    question: "Which project management knowledge areas are part of the Initiating phase?",
    answer: "Integration, Stakeholder",
    options: [
      "Integration",
      "Integration, Stakeholder",
      "Integration, Quality, Resource, Communications, Risk, Procurement, Stakeholder",
      "Integration, Scope, Schedule, Cost, Quality, Resource, Communications, Risk, Procurement, Stakeholder"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 2."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p2b",
    question: "Which processes are part of the Initiating phase?",
    answer: "project charter, stakeholder register",
    options: [
      "collect requirements, estsimate costs",
      "sequence activities, identify risks",
      "project charter, stakeholder register",
      "develop management plan, plan stakeholder engagement"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 2."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p6a",
    question: "Identify the correct process: written document including high-level project information",
    answer: "project charter",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 6."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p6b",
    question: "Identify the correct process: at-a-glance guide to why a project is taking place",
    answer: "project charter",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 6."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p6c",
    question: "Identify the correct process: authorizes a project, but is not a binding contract",
    answer: "project charter",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 6."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p13c",
    question: "Identify the correct process: person or group whose expectations and needs must be met",
    answer: "stakeholder registry",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 13."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p6d",
    question: "Identify the correct process: may include project description, scope, business case, constraints, deliverables, stakeholders, issues, and approvals",
    answer: "project charter",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 6."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p16",
    question: "Identify the correct process: proactively manage expectations",
    answer: "stakeholder registry",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 16."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p13a",
    question: "Identify the correct process: person or group that has a business interest in the outcome of a project",
    answer: "stakeholder registry",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 13."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p13b",
    question: "Identify the correct process: person or group that exerts influence on the objectives of a project",
    answer: "stakeholder registry",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 13."
  },
  {
    numb: "601m5p14",
    question: "Identify the correct process: customers, end-users, investors/funders, management and ownership, partner groups",
    answer: "stakeholder registry",
    options: [
      "project charter",
      "stakeholder registry",
      "risk registry",
      "work breakdown structure (WBS)"
    ],
    note: "Source: PROEA 601 module 5 slide 14."
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ],
  //  note: "Source: Made up question."
  // },
];